American Psychosomatic Society Records Finding Aid
Oskar Diethelm Library
- Annual Meetings
  - Administrative Files, 1943 - 1987; Organized chronologically and by meeting location. The Society held one conference annually, most often in Atlantic City, New Jersey. For early meetings only (1943-1947), files include transcripts of conference proceedings which contain business meeting reports
    - Chicago 1944 Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 110)
    - New York City 1945 Psychosomatic Techniques as applied to Cardiovascular Diseases Proceedings (Box 110)
    - New York City 1945 Conference Proceedings (Box 110)
    - New York City 1945 Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 110, Box 111)
    - New York City 1946 Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 111)
    - New York City 1946 Conference Proceedings (Box 111)
    - New York City 1946 Conference Proceedings (Draft and Duplicates) (Box 111)
    - Atlantic City 1947 Correspondence and Abstracts (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1947 Conference Proceedings Duplicate, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1947 Papers and Discussions, Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1947 Program Committee (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1948 Methodology Session (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1948 Methodology Session Transcription Disks (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1948 Business Meeting Transcription Disks (Box 112)
    - Atlantic City 1948 Correspondence (Box 113)
    - Atlantic City 1948 Correspondence Speakers, Abstracts, Manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 113)
    - Atlantic City 1949 Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 113)
    - Atlantic City 1949 Correspondence, Hotel Arrangements, Abstracts (Box 113)
    - Atlantic City 1949 Correspondence – Speakers, Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 113)
    - Atlantic City 1950 Conflict of Meeting Dates (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1950 Program Committee Abstracts, Manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1950 Correspondence, Speakers and Press (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1950 Bills (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Special Committee, 1950 - 1951 (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Date and Place (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Speakers PM Session and Business Meeting Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 114)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Committee Rejected Papers Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 115)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Speakers AM Session Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 115)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Correspondence Sooy, Services, Inquiries, Program Iniquities (Box 115)
    - Atlantic City 1951 Bills (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Program Committee Press (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Speakers, Discussants Saturday 3-29 Manuscripts (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Speakers, Discussants Sunday 3-30 (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Rejected Papers, Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Bills (Box 115)
    - Chicago 1952 Flynn, Arrangements (Box 115)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Discussants - Papers (Box 116)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Bills (Box 116)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Submitted Papers, Accepted, Manuscripts, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Submitted Papers, Rejected, 2 folders (Box 116)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Program Committee, Manuscripts (Box 116)
    - Atlantic City 1953 Panel, Adrenal Cortex Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 116)
    - New Orleans 1954 Abstracts, Rejected, 3 folders (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Date and Place (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Bills (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Hotel Arrangements and Services (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Neurophysiologic Panel Abstracts (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Cancer Round Table, Manuscripts (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Press, Program Committee Abstracts (Box 117)
    - New Orleans 1954 Accepted Papers Abstracts (Box 117)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Bills (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Hotel Arrangements, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Abstracts, Rejected, Manuscripts (A through M), 3 folders (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Abstracts, Rejected (M through Z), 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Papers and Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Panel, Technical Innovations in Psychosomatic Research, Abstracts, Manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Press; Program Committee, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Atlantic City 1955 Date and Place (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Papers and Abstracts, Manuscripts Saturday a.m. (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Abstracts Saturday p.m. (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Abstracts Sunday a.m. (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Sunday p.m. and Tea (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Correspondence, Sunday p.m. and Tea (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Abstracts. Rejected, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Preliminary Publicity (Box 119)
    - Boston 1956 Press, Program Committee, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Atlantic City 1957 Abstracts, Rejected, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Atlantic City 1957 Abstracts, Accepted, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Atlantic City 1957 Panel, Goals in Therapy in Psychosomatic Disorders (Box 120)
    - Atlantic City 1957 Publicity (Box 120)
    - Atlantic City 1957 Program Committee (Box 120)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Publicity (Box 120)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Discussants, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Bills (Box 120)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Rejected Papers, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Cincinnati 1958 Program Committee, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Bills (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Publicity (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Abstracts, Rejects, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Correspondence regarding Dr. Anokhin (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Specificity Project, Session (Box 121)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 121, Box 122)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Discussants, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Atlantic City 1959 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Montreal 1960 Bills (Box 122)
    - Montreal 1960 Publicity, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Montreal 1960 Discussants, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Montreal 1960 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 122)
    - Montreal 1960 Panel, Contributions of Behavioral Scientists to Psychosomatic Medicine (Box 123)
    - Montreal 1960 Accepted Papers, Abstracts (Box 123)
    - Montreal 1960 Abstracts, Rejects, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Montreal 1960 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Program Committee, 3 folders (Box 123)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Discussants (Box 123)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Accepted Papers, Abstracts (Box 123)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Program Committee (Box 123)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Publicity (Box 124)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Bills (Box 124)
    - Atlantic City 1961 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 124)
    - Rochester 1962 Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 124)
    - Rochester 1962 Bills (Box 124)
    - Rochester 1962 Program Committee, 3 folders (Box 124)
    - Rochester 1962 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, Manuscripts, 5 folders (Box 125)
    - Rochester 1962 Publicity (Box 125)
    - Rochester 1962 Panel (Box 125)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Bills (Box 125)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Publicity (Box 125)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Abstracts, Rejects, 3 folders (Box 125)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Panel (Box 126)
    - Atlantic City 1963 Program Committee (Box 126)
    - San Francisco 1964 Publicity (Box 126)
    - San Francisco 1964 Abstracts, Rejected (Box 126)
    - San Francisco 1964 Abstracts, 5 folders (Box 126)
    - San Francisco 1964 Accepted Papers, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 127)
    - San Francisco 1964 Program Committee (Box 127)
    - Philadelphia 1965 Publicity (Box 127)
    - Philadelphia 1965 Abstracts Rejected, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Philadelphia 1965 Abstracts Accepted, 3 folders (Box 127)
    - Philadelphia 1965 Workshops (Box 128)
    - Philadelphia 1965 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Chicago 1966 Abstracts Accepted, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Chicago 1966 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Chicago 1966 Publicity (Box 128)
    - Chicago 1966 Abstracts Rejects, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Chicago 1966 Workshops (Box 128)
    - New Orleans 1967 Bills (Box 129)
    - New Orleans 1967 Program Committee, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - New Orleans 1967 Abstracts Accepted (Box 129)
    - New Orleans 1967 Workshops (Box 129)
    - New Orleans 1967 Rejected Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 129)
    - New Orleans 1967 Publicity, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Boston 1968 Bills (Box 130)
    - Boston 1968 Publicity (Box 130)
    - Boston 1968 Rejected Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Boston 1968 Workshops (Box 130)
    - Boston 1968 Accepted Abstracts, 4 folders (Box 130)
    - Boston 1968 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Rejected Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Accepted Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Workshops (Box 131)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Program Committee (Box 131)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Bills, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - Cincinnati 1969 Publicity (Box 131)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Bills (Box 132)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Publicity (Box 132)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Workshops (Box 132)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Program Committee (Box 132)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Rejected Abstracts, Manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Washington, D.C. 1970 Accepted Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Denver 1971 Bills, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Denver 1971 Rejected Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 133)
    - Denver 1971 Publicity (Box 133)
    - Denver 1971 Abstracts Accepted, 4 folders (Box 133)
    - Denver 1971 Workshops (Box 133)
    - Denver 1971 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Boston 1972 Bills, 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Boston 1972 Publicity (Box 134)
    - Boston 1972 Abstracts Rejected, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - Boston 1972 Abstracts Accepted, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - Boston 1972 Workshops (Box 134)
    - Boston 1972 Program Committee (Box 134)
    - Denver 1973 Publicity (Box 134)
    - Denver 1973 Abstracts and Brief Communications Rejected, 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Denver 1973 Abstracts Rejected, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Denver 1973 Brief Communications Accepted (Box 135)
    - Denver 1973 Abstracts Accepted, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Denver 1973 Workshops (Box 135)
    - Denver 1973 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Bills, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Publicity (Box 135)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Abstracts and Brief Communications Rejected, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Brief Communications Accepted (Box 136)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Abstracts Rejected, 3 folders (Box 136)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Workshops (Box 136)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Program Committee (Box 136)
    - Philadelphia 1974 Accepted Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - New Orleans 1975 Rejected Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Accepted Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Brief Communications, Abstracts (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Workshops (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Program Committee (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Continuing Medical Education Workshops (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Publicity (Box 137)
    - New Orleans 1975 Brief Communications and Abstracts Accepted (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Liaison Breakfast, Chase P. Kimball (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Publicity (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Brief Communications, Abstracts (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Abstracts Rejected (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Continuing Education Workshops (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Workshops (Box 138)
    - Pittsburgh 1976 Program Committee (Box 138)
    - Atlanta 1977 Brief Communications (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Abstracts Rejected (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Abstracts Accepted (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Program Committee (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Bills, 2 folders (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Publicity (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Workshops, Liaison Breakfast (Box 139)
    - Atlanta 1977 Continuing Education, 2 folders (Box 139)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Bills (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Workshops, Liaison Breakfast (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Publicity (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Brief Communications (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Rejected Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Continuing Education, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Washington, D.C. 1978 "Hotel, etc.", 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Publicity (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Brief Communications, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Abstracts Rejected, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Abstracts Accepted (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Workshops, Symposia, Breakfast Meeting, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Dallas 1979 Program Committee (Box 141)
    - New York 1980 Continuing Education (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Program Committee (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Abstracts Rejected (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Bills, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Brief Communications, Abstracts, 3 folders (Box 142)
    - New York 1980 Workshops, Symposia, Breakfasts (Box 142)
    - Cambridge 1981 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Seminars, Symposium, Workshop (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Continuing Education (Don Lipsitt, M.D.) (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Program Committee (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Publicity (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Brief Communications Rejected, Abstracts (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Brief Communications Accepted, Abstracts (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Abstracts Rejected (Box 143)
    - Cambridge 1981 Poster Session, Abstracts (Box 143)
    - Denver 1982 Poster Sessions Accepted, Abstracts, Manuscripts (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Abstracts Accepted (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Conference, Hemophilia (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Seminar, Symposium, Workshop and Strain Breakfast (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Continuing Education (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Program Committee (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Bills, 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Publicity (Box 144)
    - Denver 1982 Posters Rejected, Abstracts (Box 145)
    - Denver 1982 Brief Communications Rejected, Abstracts (Box 145)
    - Denver 1982 Brief Communications Accepted, Abstracts (Box 145)
    - Denver 1982 Abstracts Rejected (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Bills, 2 folders (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Publicity (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Posters Rejected (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Posters Accepted (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Research Reports, C-L, Abstracts (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Brief Communications Rejected, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Continuing Medical Education (Box 145)
    - New York City 1983 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 146)
    - New York City 1983 Brief Communications Accepted, Abstracts (Box 146)
    - New York City 1983 Seminar, Workshops, Symposia, Breakfast (Box 146)
    - New York City 1983 Papers Accepted (Box 146)
    - South Carolina 1984 Bills, 2 folders (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Publicity (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Program Requests (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Brief Communications Rejected, Abstracts (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Brief Communications Accepted, Abstracts (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Posters Accepted, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Posters Rejected, Abstracts (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 147)
    - South Carolina 1984 Abstracts Rejected, Manuscripts (Box 148)
    - South Carolina 1984 Seminars, Breakfast Meeting (Box 148)
    - South Carolina 1984 Continuing Medical Education (Box 148)
    - South Carolina 1984 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Brief Communications, Abstracts (Box 148)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Posters Rejected, Abstracts (Box 148)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Posters Accepted, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Abstracts Rejected, 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Brief Communications Accepted, Abstracts, 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Abstracts Accepted, 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Seminar, Symposia, Workshops, Breakfast (Box 149)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Continuing Medical Education (Box 149)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Program Committee (Box 149)
    - Washington, D.C. 1985 Bills, 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Local Committee (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Miscellaneous (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Recipients of Annual Meeting Notices (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Press (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Seminars, Workshops, Breakfast Meeting, Invited Speakers (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Corporate Donations (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Allied, Related Organizations (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Continuing Medical Education (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Audio-Visual (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 APS Committee Meeting (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Sheraton Society Hill Contact, Correspondence (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Workshops, 2 folders (Box 150)
    - Bookbinders, 1987 (Box 150)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Abstracts Accepted (Box 151)
    - Philadelphia 1987 APS Membership (Box 151)
    - Philadelphia 1987 Program Committee, 2 folders (Box 151)
  - Meeting Publications, 1942 - 1986; Arranged chronologically. Includes "Abstracts of Presentations" (1962-1975 with many gaps) and annual meeting "Programs" (1942-1986 excluding 1945 and 1970). Abstracts of presentations provide short abstracts of papers presented at meetings. Meeting programs include names of Program Committee members, officers, and Council members for that year, and basic meeting program and schedule information. Transcripts of conference proceedings of the Society's Research Committees, which also met yearly, are located in Record Group 4 - Research Activities.
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1942 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1943 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1944 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1946 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1947 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1949 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1950 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1951 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1952 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1953 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1955 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1956 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1957 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1958 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1959 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 152)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Clinic and Scientific Meeting, 1984 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 153)
    - Program, Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1962 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1963 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1964 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1965 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1967 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1968 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1969 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1970 (Box 153)
    - Abstracts of Presentations, 1974 (Box 153)
    - News of Society, Abstracts of Papers Submitted for Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 153)
- Governance
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1955 - 1983; Arranged chronologically. Contains copies of the Society's Constitution and correspondence regarding revisions to the Constitution.
    - Constitution, c. 1955 - c. 1962 (Box 154)
    - Constitution, c. 1963 - c. 1974 (Box 154)
    - Constitution, c. 1975 - c. 1983 (Box 154)
    - Constitution and Bylaws Revisions and Memoranda to Executive Committee, 1953 - 1954 (Box 154)
    - Constitution and Bylaws Revisions and Memoranda to Executive Committee, 1955 (Box 154)
  - Council, 1943 - 1986
    - Meetings and Memoranda to Council, 1943 - 1986; This series includes meeting minutes and memoranda to Council, arranged chronologically. Memoranda, produced primarily by the executive secretary of the Society, advised members of upcoming events and developments within the Society. Ballots are included in these files. The Council of the Society consists of twelve members, ten of whom serve a three-year term. The President and Secretary-Treasurer, the Editor of the Journal, the President-elect, and the immediate past President of the Society, act as ex-officio members of the Council.
      - Memoranda to Council, 1943 - 1949 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1950 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1951 - 1952 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1953 - 1954 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1955 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1956 - 1959 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1960 - 1964 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1965 - 1970 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1971 - 1974 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1975 - 1979 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1980 - 1983 (Box 155)
      - Memoranda to Council, 1984 - 1986 (Box 155)
      - Council Minutes Final Form, 1951 - 1960 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1950 - 1952 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1953 - 1956 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1957 - 1959 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1960 - 1962 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1963 - 1965 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1965 - 1970 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1970 - 1972 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1973 - 1975 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1976 - 1979 (Box 156)
      - Council Minutes Verbatim Form, 1980 - 1982 (Box 156)
    - Committees, 1943 - 1958; Arranged chronologically. Includes the minutes, slates, ballots, and administrative correspondence of the Nominating Committee of the Council, the body responsible for nominating Council members.
      - Nominating Committee, 1943 - 1945 (Box 157)
      - Nominating Committee, 1946 - 1949 (Box 157)
      - Nominating Committee, 1949 - 1950 (Box 157)
      - Nominating Committee, 1950 - 1951 (Box 157)
      - Nominating Committee, 1951 - 1952 (Box 157)